[snoring]
[metal rattling softly]
[rooster crowing]
Wayne!
- [gasps]
- Oh. fuck.
[grunting]
[screaming]
- [Faye grunting]
- [items clattering]
Dad! Rue's headed
for the barn!
[Wayne grunting]
[panting]
- [gunshot]
- [shouting]
[Grunting. groaning]
- [gunshot]
- [Rue grunting]
- [Wayne shouting]
- [gunshots]
[Wayne screaming]
[gunshot]
[groaning]
- [horse nickering]
- [banging]
[bangs. grunts echoing]
[gunshot]
[Rue coughing]
[banging continues]
[Rue] What the fuck?!
- [gunshot]
- [Rue shouting]
[gun cocking]
[Wayne screaming]
[gunshot]
[Rue panting]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[gasps]
Oh. fuck! [shouting]
[♪ dramatic music intensifying]
[Rue shouting]
[♪ music stops abruptly]
[wind whistling]
[rope zipping]
- [panting]
- [hoofbeats thudding]
[Rue shouting]
No. no. no. no!
[Rue screaming]
- [gunshot]
- [Harley grunting]
[horse whinnying]
[♪ dramatic music resumes]
[Rue panting]
[voice] Run!
Hurry your ass up and run!
[Harley groaning]
[Rue wincing]
[Harley groaning loudly]
[groaning continues]
[Rue] [softly]
Oh. fuck. man.
[Harley] Help!
Help!
Wayne!
[Rue panting]
- [G] There you go.
- Thank you. thank you.
thank you.
- Whoo! Whoo!
- I'm a cold motherfucker!
- Baby. I swear to God!
- Whoo!
- Oh. shit!
- [laughing]
Damn!
My motherfucking heart
was beating out
my motherfucking chest!
- Yo. me too. bro!
- Damn!
Did you see?
He fucking got me. dude.
- He got me.
- Fuck. did you see?
I got him!
Motherfucker.
I was like. bow!
- Motherfucker!
Sit your ass down!
- You got his ass.
[♪ music playing faintly]
[spoon tinkling]
[server] Here you go.
What do I do?
[sniffling]
We'll figure it out together.
[Maddy sighs. sniffles]
[♪ soft. tense music playing]
[bag rustling]
Good work.
I'm proud of you.
Come here.
[kiss smacking]
Come on. have a seat.
- [wincing softly]
- Easy now.
[softly] Oh. fuck.
You know. I think
you was right all along.
About what?
You and me...
we was meant to be.
- [fridge door opens]
- [bottles clinking]
- [fridge door closes]
- [bottle cap popping]
[soda fizzing]
You look like
you're in pain.
'Cause I am.
[Rue sighs]
Percocet.
I take 'em for my back.
Mm.
You know.
Laurie knows it was me.
[Alamo] Hm.
Yeah. that bitch thought
she had the upper hand.
But little did she know.
I could train
a motherfucking mule
to win the Kentucky Derby.
- Oh. [chuckles softly]
- [chuckles]
Yeah. I could have fucked
that bitch up real good.
But I'm a gentleman.
No need to gloat.
So. I propose a 50/50 split
of the load...
and a lifetime truce.
[Alamo grunting]
But it's still going.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Matter of fact.
they should be sailing
into America tonight.
I used to love these.
[chuckles]
Hey. now.
That's for the physical pain.
Not that shit up in your head.
You hear me?
[chuckles]
[sighs]
- [exhales sharply]
- I meant what I said.
I don't want you
fucking around too much.
You're my employee
of the year.
Matter of fact.
I want you to take a week off.
- Yeah.
- Go home. relax.
Run yourself
a nice Epsom salt bath.
You need stitching up.
you send me the bill.
I got you.
Just need you to heal up.
How are we looking?
- [G] Shit all there.
- [chuckles]
Go ahead. take a peek.
[Rue exhales sharply]
Just a little token
of my appreciation.
Rest up.
Don't come back asking me
for more of that shit.
[chuckles]
G.
- [G] What's happening?
- [Alamo] It's good.
[♪ soft. tense music playing]
[money counting machine
whirring]
[birds squawking]
[people speaking Spanish]
- [urine splashing]
- [dog barking]
[child on TV]
Could I see it again?
[power tool whirring]
You promised you'd
show me how to shoot.
[people chattering indistinctly]
I know it hurts.
I'm okay.
[sighs deeply]
Alright. Go get the girls.
We should both go.
And leave this van?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[door bell jingling]
Hola. I'm here for some girls.
Sigame.
We good.
[sighs]
Gracias.
[♪ suspenseful music
continues]
[van engine starting]
[groaning]
Andale.
Where's my Coke?
Thought you were done.
I wasn't done.
Sorry.
Let's just get the fuck
out of here. man.
[TV playing faintly]
How do so many people
get to be so evil?
It's easier.
What. it's easier to do
the wrong thing
than it is to do
the right thing?
[chuckles] It's human nature.
We're selfish.
Yeah. well. why did God
make us like that?
I don't know. Rue.
But someday.
I'll ask Him for you. okay?
[Rue chuckles]
Now. get out!
[screaming]
[crowd clamoring]
Do you mind if I sit on
your couch for a little while?
Of course. you can.
It's always yours.
Thanks.
[engine rumbling]
[♪ upbeat music playing
on radio]
Kill the engine.
[engine stops]
- How you doing tonight?
- Every day is a blessing. sir.
Ah. here are our passports...
[grunting]
...and our medical pass.
- Where are you headed?
- Just outside Los Angeles.
What are you transporting?
A couple young ladies
who weren't satisfied
with what God gave 'em.
[chuckles]
[Indistinct radio chatter]
[whispering]
Hey. fix your shit.
- Name?
- Edward Wallace.
You.
- Name.
- Mitchel. Bilster.
Remain seated. please.
Hi.
- Your name?
- Kitty.
No Kitty here.
Oh. my God. I'm so stupid.
Katherine.
Christina.
You have any narcotics
or weapons in the vehicle?
Absolutely not.
No. sir.
[sighs]
Welcome back home.
Thank you.
[engine starting]
[♪ upbeat music
playing on radio]
[gong ringing]
[narrator] [on phone]
In the beginning.
God created the heavens
and the earth.
The earth was without form
and void.
and darkness was on
the face of the deep.
And the spirit of God
was hovering
over the face of the waters.
Then. God said...
"Let there be light."
And there was light.
And God saw the light.
that it was good.
And God divided the light
from the darkness.
God called the light day.
and the darkness.
He called night.
- [bird squawking]
- [Harley] I didn't let her
out of that room.
- Did you. Bruce?
- [Bruce Sr.] Fuck. no!
- Laurie?
- No.
[Harley] Could Mitch
have done it?
Mitch ain't here.
So. if it wasn't you.
using the laws
of deductive reasoning.
that only leaves one person.
But Faye's the one
who woke me up.
Oh. speak of the devil.
Here we go again.
You got a long. thin tapeworm
hanging out of your ass.
Ew! You're so gross.
Go on. get high.
That's a great fuckin' idea.
If you can't get justice
one way. get it another.
[phone buzzing]
Mitch?
Mm-hmm.
Okay. bye.
They're 30 minutes out.
About fuckin' time.
[DEA agent] [on radio]
Package is en route.
Air wing has the eye.
Copy that.
Can't wait to nail
these fuckers to a cross.
[car engine starting]
[loose flatulence]
- [loose flatulence continues]
- [water splashing]
Oh. fuck.
Fuck! Shit!
- Oh. fuck. my stomach!
- [Faye] I told you.
Bougie. get the fuck
outta here!
If they were painkillers.
you'd be constipated.
not shitting your brains out.
What the fuck
are you saying?
[Faye] They're laxatives.
Babe. we packed
the bags ourselves.
It's a set up?
In about 20 minutes.
you ought to be dead.
After that. I won't have
much trouble finding a man
who's already wounded.
- [cage clattering]
- [bird squawking]
[dog yipping]
- [TV continues playing]
- [animals continue calling]
[squawking and barking
continue]
They know something
we don't.
Wayne. what's your 20?
[radio static]
Answer me. boy.
where the fuck are you?
[grunting]
[horse neighing]
[horse nickering]
Go! Hyah!
[♪ ominous music playing]
[items clattering]
Wayne. if you're listening.
fuck you.
- [birds squawking]
- [dog barking]
[TV continues playing faintly]
[squawking and barking
continue]
[goat bleating]
- [sighs]
- [bleating continues]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[neighing]
[goat bleating]
[helicopter whirring faintly]
Fuck.
I can't go to prison.
- Fuck. Harley!
- I can't.
Fucking DEA. man.
[officers clamoring]
Fuck you. we should have
fucking killed you
- when we had the fucking chance.
- You think this was me?
- Fucking shit.
Yeah. it was you!
- You think this was me?
- Yeah. it was fucking you!
- These are my friends?!
- Ohh!
- Fucking idiot!
[officers shouting]
Harley!
[officers continue shouting]
- [Big Eddy] Fuck you!
- [Mitch] You set me and
my fucking people up. dog.
- [officers continue shouting]
- Hands up!
[Mitch] My hands are up!
Fuck you!
[Big Eddy]
I don't have a gun.
I don't have a gun!
DEA! DEA!
[helicopter whirring]
Hands! Hands up!
[officer] [over megaphone]
You are surrounded.
Surrender your weapons.
Comply with the officers
and walk out
the front door.
[dog barking]
[agent]
Got two suspects
detained.
We're loading them
in the BearCat.
[dog whining]
What are you gonna do. boy?
- Move! Move!
- Moving in!
Targets on lock!
[Bruce Sr.]
I'm not going back
to prison. bro.
Give me the word.
I'll take every last pig out.
- [officer] DEA! DEA!
- [overlapping shouting]
Hands in the air!
Drop that weapon!
Slide the weapon!
[officers shouting commands]
- [officer] Put down the weapon!
- [dog barking]
- Put your hands up! Do it now!
- [growling]
- Drop that weapon now!
- Do it!
Hands in the air
and drop to your knees!
[♪ intense music swells]
- ♪ A soldier of fortune
is the man ♪
- [officer] Nobody move!
- ♪ Called ♪
- Hands in the air!
- ♪ Paladin ♪
- [officers shouting]
[officer]
Get your fucking hands up!
Get off that bag. bitch!
Come on!
Spread out. Get out!
On your knees!
[shouting continues]
♪ Paladin. Paladin.
far. far from home ♪
[officer]
Get down. Down.
[helicopter whirring]
[officer in helicopter]
I got a target on the roof
attempting to escape.
[officer] Whoa. whoa. whoa!
[shouting indistinctly]
[officer 2] She's on the roof!
On the roof!
[Jimenez] What the fuck
is she doing?
- Get away from the ledge!
- Get down!
Step down from the roof!
Step away from the edge
of the roof.
- [rope thuds]
- [squelching]
[bottle rattling]
[rattling continues]
[power tool whirring]
[metal clanging]
[grunting]
Pork chops and pussy's
on me tonight. boys.
[chuckles]
- [goat bleating]
- [radio chatter]
[Indistinct chatter]
[goat bleating]
[bird squawking]
Tell Alamo that I'm looking
forward to meeting him one day.
You tell him yourself.
I quit.
[vehicle approaching]
[passenger indistinct]
[birdsong]
[sighs]
[cigarette pack rustling]
[lighter clattering]
[announcer] [on TV]
It's a historic day
for SpaceX.
The nearly 400-foot
Starship rocket
launched from
South Texas today.
It is the first ever
attempt at using
the novel catching method.
You're up early.
I couldn't-- couldn't sleep.
How's the hand?
Uh. yeah. it's better.
- Cool.
- And now. breaking news
from Corcoran
Correctional Facility.
where last night
a prisoner broke out.
employing a method
authorities described
as unconventional.
Patrick "Fezco" O'Neill
was serving a life sentence
for murder.
The inmate was last seen near
the facility's east perimeter
after using what appears
to be parkour
to climb the wall and escape.
Law enforcement agencies
have launched
- a full-scale manhunt...
- Oh. my God. he did it.
Oh. my God.
Holy shit. holy shit.
holy shit.
- He did it!
- What?
Ali. he fucking did it.
he did--
- What?
- Are you seeing this right now?
- Yeah. what?
- Oh. my God!
Oh. my God.
I-- I have to go get him!
- Go get him? That--
- Yes!
- What? No.
- Listen. I promised him
that if he ever got out.
I would go pick him up.
- I have to go.
- Okay. you're thinking crazy.
- You're not thinking
straight. okay?
- No. I'm not.
I know where he's hiding. man.
I gotta go.
Well. what are you gonna do.
pick up an escaped convict?
Come on. now.
Ali. you said it yourself.
"Rain or shine."
- Yeah. but I didn't mean--
- Shit. Oh. my God.
Rue!
Framing the proposal
as a cornerstone
of his closing argument against
Vice President Kamala Harris.
Latest polls show
a deadlocked race
between candidates
Trump and Harris.
Arizona remains one of
the most closely watched
battleground states.
with both campaigns
investing heavily
in the weeks ahead
of November's election.
Come on. Fez. come on.
Come on. bro.
Fucking red!
Oh. fuck.
Come on. come on.
Fuck!
[horn honking]
- Come on.
- [horn honking]
It's green! Let's go!
- Let's go!
- [engine revving]
[groaning]
Come on.
come on. come on.
[car horn honking]
[siren blaring in distance]
[brakes squealing]
[♪ somber music playing]
[inaudible]
[♪ somber music
continues]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[thuds]
[brakes screeching]
[tires screeching]
[police radio chatter]
- Yeah. I. uh. I need
to get through there.
- [both] Sorry. ma'am.
- The alley is closed down.
- I understand that.
but. like. that's my house.
- Yeah. the alley is closed.
You can't come down this way.
- Yeah. but that's my house.
- No. look! The pink house...
- The alley is closed. ma'am.
- Ma'am. you need to calm down.
- It's my fucking house!
But I already went
to the other side.
they said I couldn't go.
- and I came over here.
- You're gonna have to
wait till it's open up.
- So I just can't go home?
- That's correct.
- Okay. Whatever.
- You're gonna have
to wait. ma'am.
- Okay.
- It's unsafe.
- [Rue exclaiming]
- We got a runner
down the alley!
- [Rue] [grunting] Oh. shit.
- [officer] Go. go. go. go.
- [officer shouting]
- Fez!
- Fez! Fez!
- [siren chirping]
[officer] She's going up
on the roof.
[panting]
- [dog barking]
- [sirens blaring]
[♪ soft. gentle music playing]
[grunting softly]
[♪ soft. dramatic music playing]
[♪ dramatic music swelling]
[♪ somber vocal music playing]
[voice echoing]
Mom?
[gasping]
[♪ somber vocal music
continues]
[chuckles weakly]
[sobbing]
[labored breathing]
[♪ somber vocal music
continues]
[sobbing]
[labored breathing continues]
[♪ somber vocal music
continues]
[sighs]
[cigarette pack rustling]
[lighter clattering]
[♪ somber vocal music
continues]
Rue?
Rue.
[sighing weakly]
[Ali] [whispering]
Give her peace.
[sighs]
God.
[soft kiss]
[♪ somber vocal music
continues]
[clock ticking]
[♪ somber vocal music ends]
[banging table]
[sighs]
Hey. Leslie.
It's me. Ali.
I'm calling with
some bad news.
[muffled audio]
[pen scribbling]
[sighs]
[lips smacking]
[Ali] I used to believe
that the world would be
a better place
if people could empathize
with addiction.
To understand that
addicts were suffering
from an incurable disease...
no different than cancer.
The addict may be
in remission. but that...
that disease ain't gone.
I thought that empathy
was the key.
But if you can empathize...
with an addict.
you can also empathize
with a dealer.
They're selling drugs
to feed their children.
Who can't understand that?
So maybe. uh...
empathy ain't that helpful
after all.
And maybe
the real disease...
is that people no longer
know the difference
between right and wrong.
I don't care what
your struggles may be.
You poison kids for money.
You're evil.
It's plain and simple.
[sniffling]
The number one cause of death
for people under the age
of 50...
is fentanyl.
That ain't an accident.
That's big business.
I ain't just talking
about the kid
on the corner
selling fake Percocets.
You know how many
motherfuckers
got to be complicit?
From the governments
that allow their people
to make the chemicals.
to the shipping companies
to bring that shit
across the seas.
to the dockworkers
that let that shit in.
to the cartels. the cookers.
the corrupt cops.
the fucking bureaucrats
at the border.
the nonprofits who justify it.
and the lawyers
and politicians
who defend it all.
A couple of months ago...
I lost someone
I really cared about.
And for the first time
in a long time...
I picked up a drink.
I didn't even know
what to do with the pain.
I've been a Christian.
a Muslim.
And suddenly. I found myself
not believing in shit.
But that ain't it either.
I just know that I'm tired.
Tired of losing people.
Tired of spending my life
in these rooms.
and in diners. and...
at my house.
Talking to kids.
Helping kids.
Pouring my fucking
heart and soul into kids.
Only to not see them get
a second chance.
I'm done.
Only thing
I know for certain
is that there is a right
and a wrong in this world.
There ain't no in between.
You're either making
the world a better place
or you're making it worse.
In the end.
it's that fucking simple.
This is gonna be
my last meeting.
I'm gonna find another way
to be of better service.
[saw grinding]
[rod thuds]
[blowing]
[gun cocking]
[♪ gentle music playing]
[♪ gentle music
continues playing]
[soft kiss]
[Cassie]
Green makes you
wanna online shop.
Blue makes you sleepy.
Yellow gets you excited.
But caramel makes you horny.
Couples with caramel
in their homes
are three times
more likely to have sex.
Apparently. it tricks your brain
into thinking about pleasure
due to its association
with indulgent foods.
Are you sure you don't wanna
just sell this place?
[Cassie]
I owe more than it's worth.
but I think that's a good thing.
How is that a good thing?
Mm. because it forced me to
put on my entrepreneurial hat.
We concept everything
for the girls.
photoshoots. videos.
hair. makeup.
In exchange. we just
charge room and board
and take a cut
of everything they make.
The only thing we're missing
is a storyteller.
A-And that's me?
[buttons beeping]
[lock clacking]
[safe door closes]
[♪ soft music playing]
[lipstick capsule popping]
[lips smacking softly]
Don't wait up for me.
I'll be late.
It'll be easier
if you pretend to like him.
[engine rumbling]
- [♪ music playing
faintly on radio]
- [dog panting]
What's its name?
- Snowflake.
- That's cute.
I agree.
So you got yourself
a girlfriend?
It's a boy.
You give him this haircut?
I wouldn't have thought of you
as a poodle man.
Why?
I don't know. you kinda give me
the Doberman type.
I like to surprise people.
You know what
I would find surprising?
A little grace in this world.
Do you think
Nate's ever gonna come back?
Um...
I don't know.
I hope so.
- Do you miss him?
- Of course.
Be weird if I didn't.
But like. the mystery of it.
Him just disappearing?
That doesn't keep you
up at night?
I don't like to think about it.
You ever read the Bible?
No. why?
Rue left it on the couch.
I'd wake up in the morning
to go to work.
make a cup of coffee.
There it was. just...
looking at me.
What do you mean.
looking at you?
Just sitting there.
right where she left it.
Mm. That's really spooky.
Yeah.
I almost threw it out.
but that felt like a worse omen.
So you just left it there?
After like a month or so.
I worked up the courage
to move it to the bookshelf.
but that didn't do anything.
And I still had this creepy
Bible in my apartment.
so I was like. fuck it.
I guess I'll read it.
And what'd it say?
A lot of things.
It's kind of incredible. actually.
Like. you'd think
it'd be boring.
but there's a lot
of violence and sex.
So there's a new Bible?
No. it's the same Bible.
So. the old one?
Yeah.
Was it any good?
- It's kind of beautiful.
- Hm.
A little confusing.
but fascinating and...
I don't know. it just had me
thinking about a lot of stuff.
Like what?
Just that certain things
aren't my fault.
Not that I'm without faults.
but...
[softly] Uh...
Rue?
I think...
I've just had a lot of guilt
about how I left things.
like I could have--
I could have left things better.
She was a drug addict.
Yeah. I know.
It's kind of like Dad.
The last thing he ever said
to me was. "I love you."
Didn't make it any easier.
So it doesn't matter
how you leave things.
It still sucks.
Yeah. but that's the thing.
Like. after Dad.
I spent the next ten years
worrying that was
gonna happen again.
To who?
To me. that I'd...
lose someone and...
What does this
have to do with the Bible?
In the Bible. everyone's dying
of all different things.
and they just keep going.
And that's the heart of it.
I think.
Bad things happen.
So. why have
anxiety about it?
Like. what good does it do?
No matter what. you have
to just keep going. and...
that's the point of it. I think.
She had a really nice smile.
Rue?
Yeah.
I think a smile
says a lot about a person.
When you smile.
other people smile.
It's contagious.
[laughing]
So you wanna work together?
[sniffling]
I appreciate the offer.
but I...
think I have to figure
some stuff out first.
Are you saying no
because of the Bible?
[laughing] I don't know.
I think I have
to read it again.
[door closes]
[Cassie sniffling]
[gulps. sniffles softly]
[♪ gentle music playing]
[dancer] Hell no. I'm next.
[indistinct chatter]
[customers whistling. cheering]
[♪ loud hip-hop music playing]
[waitress]
Just as you like it.
[♪ loud hip-hop music
continues playing]
♪ I wanna leave the club
right now. babe ♪
♪ I wanna leave
the club right now ♪
♪ I'm feeling this shit.
it's thumping ♪
♪ I'm finna get you
out of here ♪
[Alamo] There she is.
my favorite little CEO.
[dancer]
You like that. baby.
[music and chatter continue]
♪ Ooh. baby. please.
buss it open. show me. babe ♪
buss it for a real player ♪
♪ Ooh. baby. please.
I want you how I want you ♪
♪ Ooh baby. please.
smurk ♪
♪ VIP. I'm off the mud
right now ♪
♪ My bitch text my phone.
leave the club right now ♪
♪ Make excuse.
the kids need me
I'm a do it right now ♪
♪ Quarter ticket
for the backend.
going to court right now ♪
♪ They saying
gotta watch they stories ♪
♪ Told me if I lied. then she
probably turn to Lori ♪
♪ Your friends over there.
when I pull up.
we having orgies ♪
Keep an eye on Snowflake.
- Oh. my God.
- Okay.
So adorable.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[light applause]
[♪ dramatic music
continues playing]
[snake hissing]
[♪ loud hip-hop music playing]
[lock clicking. rattling]
[music and chatter continue]
[music and chatter
muffling. fading]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
- [♪ tense music playing]
- [footsteps echoing]
[Champagne pouring]
[chuckles]
[chuckles. sniffs]
[bag thuds]
You don't want to count it?
- Nah.
- It could be a deck
of playing cards.
I had an epiphany.
- What?
- I had an epiphany.
I was sitting
at the edge of the stage
watching Kitty dance.
She tall. but limber.
And as she parted her pins
like a little marionette.
that's when it happened.
- What happened?
- My epiphany.
I dedicated my life to pussy.
Bought. sold. fucked.
devoured every shape and size.
But there I was...
staring up at Kitty's slit...
when it consumed me.
It was fear.
I might run the club.
But pussy still runs me.
Hm.
So what the fuck I been
doing all this time?
You've been
building a business.
For what?
For who?
For you.
To be free.
- Free?
- Mm-hmm.
[sighs]
I'm just another slave
with a little more money
in my hand.
- [♪ loud hip-hop music playing]
- [chattering. cheering]
I'm Kitty. and I love
a man in uniform.
Where's your manager?
You look like you just
got home from work.
Wanna let off some steam?
[gasps]
I asked for your manager.
[music and chatter continue]
[dancers chattering]
[knocking]
- [Kitty] G?
- Yeah.
There's a man here
to see you.
Tell him I got my hands full.
- [dancers chuckle]
- Can you tell him?
[music and chatter continue]
[♪ muffled music
continues playing]
[blinds rattling]
[G] Y'all keep that shit wet.
I think you just need
to lay off the merchandise.
I think it's deeper than that.
This thing that you got
between your legs?
It's a miracle.
I'm talking
white picket fences.
That Norman Rockwell
kind of life.
Cute little girl
in the kitchen...
barefoot and pregnant.
Us?
It's biblical.
You sure about that?
I want the American dream.
I'm old.
The American dream. baby.
I want it.
For our four beautiful
cocoa-colored babies. too.
[♪ loud hip-hop music playing]
What's up. soldier?
What you want?
Are you the manager?
- Who's asking?
- Me.
[Kitty] How are you?
I don't know
no motherfucking "Me."
Who is you?
A friend of Rue's.
[♪ loud hip-hop
continues playing]
[G] Well. Rue don't
work here no more.
- Why?
- People come and people go.
Is this place owned
by Alamo Brown?
You know what.
for a stranger...
you ask a lot
of motherfucking questions.
[gun cocking]
Sit your monkey ass down.
Put your hands
where I can see 'em.
Kidd. Hey. Kidd.
Hey. Kidd.
Lean in.
Now. if you lie to me...
I'm gonna blow
your motherfucking dick off.
Now. I asked you a question.
Is this place owned
by Alamo Brown?
- Mm-hmm.
- Is he here?
- Good. good.
What happened to Rue?
- She OD'd.
- How?
Fentanyl.
Who the fuck gave it to her?
I don't know.
Nigga. look at this.
You lied to me.
- [gunshot]
- [people screaming]
[screaming continues]
[Ali]
I'm here for Alamo Brown.
[dancer gasps]
[Ali]
Alamo motherfucking Brown!
Get your bitch ass out here!
[gunfire]
[grunting]
[people shouting]
- [banging]
- [shouting]
- [gun cocking]
- Alamo Brown!
Alamo.
get the fuck down here!
I ain't fucking with y'all.
- Hands where I can
fucking see 'em!
- [people shouting]
You wanna die tonight.
motherfucker?
Step up!
Drop it on the ground!
[gun thuds]
Get your dick
against the wall.
Dick against
the motherfucking wall!
I'm here for one motherfucker!
- Alamo Brown.
- [Alamo sighs]
[Ali] Alamo!
Alamo Brown!
- Bitch-ass--
- [glass shattering]
[Alamo] Someone say
my motherfucking name?
This is fucking Alamo Brown!
[♪ high-pitched. discordant
music playing]
[Maddy gasps]
Yeah. what?
Go on. shoot.
Shoot. nigga. Shoot!
You want you
some Alamo Brown?
I'll be right out.
[Maddy gasps]
Got a Remington 870. huh?
[Ali] Yeah. motherfucker.
[Alamo] I might not be the most
educated nigger on the planet...
but I do know how to count.
And you got three shots left. soldier.
And I got way more than three
armed motherfuckers up in here.
So unless you got another gun
I don't know about...
odds are...
you gonna die tonight.
I'm prepared for that.
[Alamo] You know.
you could have shot
right through that girl
and killed my Black ass
stone dead.
But you hesitated.
You a man of principle?
Bring your bitch ass
out here and find out.
[Alamo laughing]
Ladies and gentlemen.
we got us
a big swinging Mandingo dick
up in here tonight.
How 'bout this. Mandingo?
I'll give your Black ass
one fair shot of me
before my boys
blow your ass to bits.
- I'll take it.
- So go on ahead
and lower that shotgun...
and we can settle this
the old-fashioned way.
The old-fashioned way?
[chuckles] Yeah.
Word is bond.
[Alamo] Kitty?
Yeah?
That motherfucker
lower the shotgun?
Yeah.
- Bitch. I can't hear you!
- Yes!
Bitch. you don't sound
too sure.
[Kitty]
I'm sure.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
So. what's your name?
You wanna tell me
who sent you?
Rue.
So you got a score to settle.
Something like that.
Kitty.
- Kitty.
- Yeah?
Grab me a champagne bottle.
Got it.
[Alamo] It empty?
[champagne sloshing]
No.
Bring it over here.
sweet cheeks.
[champagne sloshing]
[sighs]
That's some good shit.
- You want some?
- I don't drink.
Motherfucker.
you ain't no fun.
Kitty.
Take this here bottle...
and roll it across
that bar right there.
[dancer gasps. grunts]
And when it drops...
all you motherfuckers
best duck.
[glass breaking]
'Cause that's when
we gonna draw.
[glass breaking]
Now how that sound?
Fine by me.
Just so we're clear...
guns stay down
till that bottle shatters now.
No cheatin'.
[Alamo]
Alright. Kitty cat.
Let that motherfucker roll.
One Mississippi.
Two Mississippi.
Three Mississippi.
[bottle rolling]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[bottle continues rolling]
[gasps softly]
[gun clicking]
[♪ suspenseful music
stops abruptly]
[shattering]
I'll see you in hell.
you motherfu--
[gunshot]
[♪ epic dramatic music playing]
[body thuds]
[chuckles softly]
[gurgling]
Just in case.
[gunshot]
[dancer whimpering]
May God have mercy.
Can I give you
a ride home?
[♪ Western music playing]
[chickens clucking]
[horse whinnying]
How can I help you?
My daughter stayed here
a while back.
She said it was the most
peaceful place she'd ever been.
[Daisy] Ruby?
- Yeah.
- How is she?
[sighs]
She's in a better place.
[Mr. Miller] Well. I'm--
I'm sorry to hear that.
What's your name?
Martin.
Martin McQueen.
Pleasure to meet you. Martin.
Why don't you come in?
Let's have some coffee and...
talk a bit. hm?
[♪ gentle music playing]
[♪ gentle music
continues]
♪
[horse nickering]
She just had her baby
three months ago.
It's a miracle.
You hungry?
Follow me.
[Mr. Miller]
Martin. would you please
lead us in grace?
Father...
I pray today
for those whose eyes
have grown weak with sorrow...
whose soul and body
are weighed down by grief...
and whose
strength is failing.
Lord. pour out
Your mercy upon them.
Let Your face shine upon them
and save them
in Your unfailing love.
[sighs]
Thank you. Rue.
Let her memory be a blessing.
Amen.
[chuckles softly]
[whispering] Amen.
[family] Amen.
[♪ gentle music
continues playing]
♪
[Rue]
May God bless us all.
[♪ gentle music
continues playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm